## Hello

## I'm Fo'ad Salmanian

Shahin Shahr, Isfahan +98 936 144 6386 SALMANIAN.FOAD2@GMAIL.COM

## Skills



# **Experience**

August 2021 - Present

Freelance web developer - Fullstack Developer

June 2017 - August 2021

Front-end web developer, chatbot developer, add-on developer

- During my four years in this company I have worked as a frontend developer using classic HTML/CSS/JS and reactJS
- One of the projects was a smart chatbot which we developed using Dialogflow for NLP and Nodejs for its webhook

- We also developed a google sheet add-on for creating visual graphs using graphviz
- One of my favorite tasks was trying to write documentations and guidelines for coding and tools like git. They meant to help team members become more organized and enable them to be more efficient.
- Due to company policies, I cannot share any information about the company or the projects that I have worked on with them

April 2020 - June 2020

#### **Iran Ahana** *- Fullstack Developer*

- This was a 2 month project, a website for a travel agency
- Everything on this project was done by me except for its graphic design
- To keep the expenses low, the designs for this project was kept to a bare minimum
- This project was cancelled due to issues with PO and my underestimation of the situation

August 2015 - October 2015

#### **Sejam** - Backend developer

- This was a two month project, a website to track different individuals' credit score
- It never made it to production stage due to legal problems it died in the middle of development
- This was my first-ever project which was done using Django

## **Education**

Programming is something that I can remember constantly learning ever since I was 15 or 16 years old. Mostly self taught, and I still prefer it that way.

I studied Engligh Language Studies for 7 years before dropping out. Yet, my English language skills persist.

I've been pursuing business development and project management as a side education. It started with a course done by Cast Plan and continued through different sources of study and experience.

#### **About Me**

Mistakes are a part of my workflow. I experience them, admit them, learn from them, make up if necessary, and move on. If there is room in your team for making mistakes, then there is room for growth, and that is where I would very much like to be.